剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
门前有辆租来的车  你开车去Sioux城
There's a rental car parked out front. Got to Sue city.
然后去Sage Flower汽车旅馆
I want you to check in at the Sage Flower motel.
在那儿等我  我明天一早就来
Wait for me. I'll be there in the A.M.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
-I love you.  -I love you, too.
快走...
Go...
我不管Jack都说了什么
I don't care what Jack said.
我们要把他救回来  这是我欠他的
They've got him, and we have to get him back. I owe him that.
很显然  现在情况有所变化
Obviously, the circumstances have changed.
他也许不希望我们来救他
He may not want to be rescued.
他在跟"the others"握手
If he's shaking hands with the others,
我相信他有自己的理由
I'm sure he has a good reason.
我们是来救Jack的  现在可以行动了
We came here to rescue Jack, and that's what we're gonna do.
你来这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
- 我是来救你的  - 快离开这儿
-I came to get you.  -Get outta here.
别伤害她
Don't hurt her!
我和他们做了笔交易  他们答应放我走
I made a deal with them.They're gonna let me go.
去哪里?
Where?
回家
Home.
Jack  我们该走了
Jack, we need to go.
呆在那儿别动
Hey, hold it right there!
把手举起来  跪下  我叫你跪下
Get your hands up! Get down! I said get down!
- 你在这儿做什么  John?  - 我很抱歉  Jack
-What are you doing here, John?  -I'm sorry, Jack.
为什么?
Sorry for what?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：    许愿
校对： 许愿
■
双语字幕：    七色九天
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
我只是来给你送点吃的
I was just bringing you something to eat.
好好享受你的三明治吧
Enjoy your sandwich.
I go out walkin' after midnight...
等很久了吧?
Been on the road a while, huh?
还要多久?
How long is it gonna take?
你的挡风玻璃被射穿了  估计要两天
Well, your fan belt's shot. I'll take two days,
也许要三天
maybe three.
换这个要用三天?
Three days for a fan belt?
欢迎来到Iowa城
Welcome to Iowa.
searchin' for you...
我叫Johnny
My name is Johnny.
我叫Lucy
I'm Lucy.
along the highway
well, that's just my way
of sayin' I love you
I'm always walkin'...
全都是18K的
All 18-karat gold.
最便宜也要500块
Cheapest one in retail for 500 bucks.
拜托  一看就知道是假的  我才不买呢
Come on. Those don't look real. I'm not buying.
你什么意思  看起来像假的?
What do you mean, they don't look real?
听着  如果不是我伯父破产了  你绝对买不到...
My uncle's going out of business.
如果你要进城的话  我马上就来
If you need a lift into town, I'm finished up here in an hour.
- 快报警  - 好吧  随便你  这是你自己的损失
-I call the cops.  -Fine. Whatever. Your loss.
- 有什么问题吗  伙计?  - 是啊  她想骗我的钱
-Is there a problem, buddy?  -Yeah, there's a problem.I'm getting scammed here,
- 就这么回事  - 听着  我很抱歉
-that's the problem.  -Look, I'm sorry.
你当我是白痴吗
What do you think, I'm an idiot?
伙计  如果你不想买就算了
If you don't want to buy them, don't buy them.
这些项链是假的  你是个骗子
Those are fake necklaces, and you're a rip-off artist.
- 这些都是真的  - 快报警吧!
-They're real.  -Call the cops.
如果你不买有人会来买的
You don't want them, I'll find somebody else.
拿来让我看看
Hey, let me see those.
我父亲是开珠宝店的
My father owns a jewelry store.
我能辨别真伪  多少钱?
I think I can spot a fake.How much?
60块
60 bucks.
我买一条
I'll take the one on the end.
随便你吧!
Whatever.
没什么
Yeah.
能把钱还我了吗?
Can I get my money back?
你为什么要帮我?
Why'd you help me?
没什么  只是一个女孩帮助另一个女孩
Just one girl watching another girl's back, I guess.
我猜出于什么原因
Or you're stranded here,
你也被困在这儿了
and for some reason,
你不希望那人去报警
you didn't want that guy calling the cops.
我载你进城吧  但你要请我喝酒
I'll give you a ride into town. You buy me a drink.
什么事?
What?
Kate
John?
你在这儿做什么?
What are you doing?
你被他们抓了吗?
Did they capture you?
是的  不过...
Yes, but...
那只是暂时的
Only temporarily.
我是来和你告别的
I came to say good-bye.
告别?
Good-bye?
- 我要跟他们走了  - 究竟发生了什么事?
-I'm leaving with them.  -What the hell is going on?
他们把你怎么了  你被洗脑了吗?
I mean, what are they doing to you? Are you brainwashed?
- Jack去哪了?  - Jack哪也没去  Kate
-Where did Jack go?  -Jack didn't go anywhere, Kate.
和你一样  他也会被留在这里
He's gonna have to stay behind, like you.
你不能相信他们
You can't trust them.
如果他们答应你带你回家
If they told you that they're gonna take you home,
- 他们是在撒谎...  - 我不想回家
-they're lying...  -I don't want to go home.
希望你明白  我一直对你很放心
I want you to know, I made a strong case for you.
我告诉他们你是个好人
I told them that you were a good person.
可靠  聪明  诚实
reliable, smart, honest.
然而他们告诉我你是谁  还有你的所作所为
And then they told me who you were and what you had done.
看来我并不擅长于宽恕
Let's just say, forgiveness isn't one of their strong suits.
祝你好运
Good luck.
John  你要去哪?
John, where are you going?
我出来了
Coming out!
Jack在哪  还有Sayid
Where is Jack and where is Sayid?
你有没有看见Rousseau
Have you seen Rousseau?
Jonh  你到底怎么了?
John, please. What's happened to you?
我很抱歉  Kate
I'm sorry, Kate.
你有病啊?
What the hell's wrong with you?
不要看着我  就假装我们没在说话
Don't look at me, and pretend we're not talking.
- 我本不该来找你的  - 很好  那就快滚开
-I'm not supposed to be here.  -Good. Then scram.
伙计  大家最近都在议论你
Dude, you need to know that there's been some chatter.
关于Paulo和Nikki的死  还有近来发生的一切
After Paulo and Nikki and everything,
是这样的  明天大家会进行投票
Well, tomorrow there's gonna be a vote.
- 投什么票  - 投票是否该赶走你
-A vote for what?  -To decide whether or not to banish you.
赶我走?
Banish me?
到哪里去?
Where?
大家还在商量
Well, there was debate about that,
- 但大多数人认为应该让你去半里外的那个海滩  - 大多数人
-but the consensus was half a mile down the beach.  -Consensus?
我来是想告诉你  你还是有机会留下的
I'm only saying this because there may be a way to fix it
比如说婉转的道歉
to, like, make amends.
我才不道歉呢
I don't do amends.
你自己想想
You might want to ask yourself
我们这个群体
about all the good stuff that comes from being
为你提供了很多好处
part of this... society.
你自己根本无法独立生存
I mean, you can't even feed yourself.
你用我们建的厕所
You use our latrine,
喝的是Steve每天早上运来的水...
drink the water that Steve brings every morning to the trough...
怎么了?
What?
我已经3天10小时15分钟
You know how for 3 days, 10 h and 15 min
没有叫你们绰号了
I ain't allowed to use nicknames?
是啊
Yeah.
那么  你  Hugo先生
Well, you, sir... Hugo,
是一个"小胖"
are rotund,
讨厌的家伙
annoying,
你还破坏了我的景致
and you're ruining my damn view.
这样道歉怎么样?
How's that for amends?
你犯了个大的错误  兄弟
You're making a big mistake, dude.
赶我走...
Banish me...
告诉我你的名字吧
How about you tell me your name?
我叫Lucy
It's Lucy.
那你的真名是什么?
And what's your real name?
- 下次有人问的时候  你不必去想  - 我没有去想
-Next time somebody asks, you don't think about it.  -I didn't think
别骗我了
Not even for a second.
为什么叫Lucy
So why Lucy?
她是个圣女
She's a saint.
我上主日学校的时候  都要背诵那些名字
I had to memorize them all in Sunday's school,
我发现直到现在
so I figure they're probably still
我还一直没有忘记它们
rattling around my brain.
那是什么让一个上主日学的女孩
What makes a girl who went
害怕起警察来的?
to Sunday school scared of cops?
几个月前我杀了我的继父
A few months ago, I killed my stepfather.
还从警官手里逃走了
I escaped from the marshal who arrested me for it.
为什么?
Why?
因为他是个坏人
'cause he was a bad guy.
那么你在Iowa做什么?
So...what the hell are you doing in Iowa?
我想和我母亲谈谈
I want to talk to my mother.
那你在这里可得小心了
You're gonna have a really hard time doing that,
因为如果你真的要这样做的话
because if you did what you just said you did,
联邦探员们会一直监视她的
the feds are gonna be watching her 24/7.
- 我会想出办法的  - 是吗?
-I'll figure something out.  -Oh, you will, huh?
你打算帮我吗?
What, you want to help me?
当然
Absolutely.
为什么?
Why?
我爱上了一个不该爱的人
I fell in love with the wrong guy,
然后我把我这辈子的积蓄都给了他
and then I gave him my life savings.
他却骗我  这让我难堪
He conned me and embarrassed me.
他也是个坏人
He was a bad guy.
所以...
So...
我会帮你见到你母亲的  Lucy
I'll help you get the meeting with your mom... Lucy,
总有一个人要交好运的
because one of us deserves something good.
看来我得不到韩国人的票了
I ain't gonna get the Korean vote.
我们开始吧!
All right, let's do it!
什么?
Do what?
我准备好向大家道歉了
I'm ready to do it: make amends,
努力改变现状
change the vote.
我可不想被赶跑
I don't wanna be banished, okay?
你高兴了吧
You happy?
伙计  你真臭
Dude, you stink.
什么来的  鱼吗?
What is that, fish?
才不是
No.
你刚自己杀鱼?
Did you try to gut one yourself?
你怎么到现在都还没有学会啊?
How have you not learned that by now?
我们到这里都三个月了
I mean, we've been here, like, three months.
别废话了  我们开始吧
Could we just do this?
做什么?
Do what?
与人为善
Make nice?
先为刚才你叫我绰号道歉
Apologize for calling me all those names.
我很抱歉叫你"小胖"
I'm really sorry I called you "rotund."
真的?
Really?
天啊  你比女孩还坏
You're worse than a girl.
拜托
Come on.
我们去传达关爱吧
Let's spread the love.
我怎么会在这儿?
What the hell am I doing here?
- 你来告诉我  - 我不知道
-Why don't you tell me?  -I don't know.
我也不知道
I don't know either!
所以你不如先放开我的手
So, why don't you let go of my wrist?
到底发生了什么事?
So what the hell happened?
我正在泡茶
I was making a cup of tea.
一个瓦斯罐扔了进来
Canister came in through the window.
你做了什么让他们这么生气?
So what'd you do to piss them off?
你这是在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
刀口太大了
The knife is too big.
我们需要小点的东西 比如别针什么的...
We need something smaller. A safety pin...
- 我们要回去  - 什么?
-We're going back.  -What?
他们这样对待我们  你还想回去?
They did this to us. Why would we go back?
你说"他们"  好像当初是你把我关进笼子的
You say "they" like you didn't lock me in a cage
还整天看着我碾碎石头
and watch me break rocks all day.
我们要回你的村子是因为
We're going back to your village because
我的朋友也可能中了瓦斯弹  就像我们一样
my friends were probably gassed, just like us.
反正你的人都已经走了
Your people are gone anyway.
- 我看到他们打包走了  - 什么?
-I saw them all pack up and leave.  -What?
Locke来向我告别
Locke came to me to say good-bye.
他们去别的地方了
They were taking off, going somewhere else.
走了?  去哪儿?
Going? Going where?
他没说
He didn't exactly tell me.
欢迎你来到茫然的世界
Welcome to the wonderful world of not knowing what the hell's going on.
快!
Go,go,go!
趴下!
On the ground!
趴下  趴在地上
Get down! On the ground!
把手举起来
Let me see those hands!
好久不见了  Austen
Long time no see, Austen.
你是谁?
Who the hell are you?
我只是来卖圣经的
I'm just selling bibles!
他们盘问了我半个小时
They questioned me for half an hour.
还拿走了我的手提包
He confiscated my case.
问我卖圣经的事还有...
He was asking me about selling bibles and...
还好我知道该怎么撒谎
It's a good thing I know how to lie.
现在我们知道面对的是什么人了
Yeah, now we know what we're up against, right?
现在我们知道有六个人在等着抓你  Lucy
Yeah, now we know that there were six guys waiting to take you down, Lucy
没关系  我会想办法的
Yeah, it's okay. I'll figure it out.
想办法?  那个警官
Figure it out? That marshal
我不知道你对他干了什么
I don't know what you did to him,
但如果他再抓到你的话
but if he ever gets his hands on you,
到时不是你死就是他亡
it is gonna be you or him.
如果你改变了主意
Look, if you've changed your mind,
如果你不想帮我了 我能理解
if you don't wanna help me, I get it.
不  我想帮你
No, I do wanna help you,
如果要我对联邦探员撒谎  Lucy
but if I'm lying to federal agents, Lucy,
让你能和你母亲见面的话...
so that you can have a chat with your mom...
那至少给我一个
then I at least need to know
好的理由
that there's a pretty good reason.
他过去经常酗酒还殴打我妈妈
He... used to get drunk and beat up my mom,
所以我炸了他的房子
so I blew up his house.
我...
I...
把那次爆炸做的像场意外
Made it look like an accident.
一次煤气泄漏
a gas leak.
我领取了房子的保险金...
Took out an insurance policy on the house...
为了她
for her.
让她能过上好日子
Set her up for life.
但是她却举报了我
And then she gave me up.
反而选择了他
Chose him over me.
我要和她谈谈的原因是...
So the reason I need to talk to her is...
某个我爱的人...
someone I love...
某个应该关心我的人
Someone who's supposed to care about me
却背叛了我
betrayed me,
我要知道为什么
and I wanna know why.
好吧
Well
我们一起去找出答案吧
then let's go find out.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
他们应该会留下些踪迹
Whoever dragged us out here left a trail.
那可以帮我们找到回去的路
It'll lead us back to where we came from.
马上要下雨了
Let's go.It's gonna rain.
你不认为我们应该等到明天再走吗?
Don't you think we should wait till morning?
不
No.
为什么?
Why?
什么为什么?
Why what?
为什么他们把我们铐在一起
Why would they handcuff you to me
然后还把我们拖进丛林?
and then drag us all the way out into the jungle?
Ben很擅长玩心理游戏
Ben has a thing for mind games.
这就是他把你丢下的原因?
Is that why he left you behind?
我们一定要讨论这个吗?
Do we really have to talk?
不
Nope.
快点  如果地上都湿了我就找不到踪迹了
Come on. If the trail gets wet, I'll lose it.
我希望你不是为了他
I hope you're not dragging me
才把我一路拽回去
all the way back there with you for him.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
我希望你不是为了Jack而回去
I hope you're not going back for Jack,
当他对你说不要回去找他的时候
because I was standing right there
我当时在场
when he told you not to come back,
现在你又毁了他离开这里的机会
and now that you've ruined his chance to get off the island...
你讲完了没有?
You done?
我问你讲完了没有?
I said, are you done?
我...很抱歉 我不是故意...
I... I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
那是什么东西?
What the hell was that?
快起来
Get up!
我的肩膀脱臼了  起来
You dislocated my shoulder!
快点
Come on!
等等  来这边
Wait! Come here.
好了  快蹲下
Okay. Get down.
那到底是...
What the hell...
我们安全了吗?
Are we safe?
我不知道
You tell me.
我才不会亲什么小孩的
I ain't kissing no damn baby.
Claire在这里挺有人缘的
Claire's, like, really influential.
如果她选你留下  你就不用担心了
If she votes for you to stay, you're home free, dude.
她为什么会不同意
Why wouldn't she vote for me?
- 我又没有对她做过什么坏事  - 也没做过什么好事
-It's not like I ever done anything bad to her.  -but you never did anything good for her either.
你有关心过Aaron吗?
And have you ever even asked how Aaron is?
我知道他
I know how he is.
哭声又大  身上也难闻
He cries loud, and he smells.
这就是你的问题
You see? That's what I'm talking about.
你很会讽刺人  大家都不喜欢这点
You're sarcastic. People don't like that.
好吧  那我过去...
All right.So I go over...
然后怎么做?
And do what?
母亲都希望大家注意自己的宝宝
Moms love it when you show an interest in their babies.
你走过去说些好听的话
So go over there, say something nice,
叫她Claire
call her "Claire".
然后把这个给她
And give her this.
我知道你能做到的  伙计
I know you can do it, dude.
Claire
Hey, Claire
你好...小宝宝
Hey there... little baby...
Aaron
我能为你做什么吗?
Is there anything I can do for you?
不  我只是过来看看你的宝宝
No. I just came by...to see your baby.
他不像几周前皮肤还皱巴巴的拉
He's not as wrinkly as he was a couple weeks ago.
是啊  我也这么觉得  谢谢
Yeah, I... guess he's not. Thanks.
这个给你
Oh, and... this is for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不太喜欢...
I don't like...
毯子
blankets.
好吧  晚安
Well, good night.
晚安
Good night.
你认为它走了吗?
Do you think it's gone?
- 我们安全了吗?  - 你不是认真的吧
-Are we safe?  -Are you serious?
- 什么?  - 你从没见过那东西?
-What?  -You've never seen that?
如果你不相信我  你可以
If you don't believe me,you can always
把我另一只手也拽脱臼
pull my other shoulder out of its socket.
我不是...我不是故意...
I was... I wasn't trying to...
不要找借口了
Don't flatter yourself.
这是我第四次脱臼了
This is the fourth time it's been dislocated.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
为什么?
Why?
- 你要把我的肩膀复位  - 不  我不会...
-'cause I want you to pop it back in.  -No, I'm not gonna...
你必须这么做  我现在就感觉
You're gonna.Right, now it feels
像有碎玻璃扎在里面似的
like there's broken glass under my skin,
如果不是因为你们
and if it weren't for you,
我早就在回家的路上了
I would be on my way home right now.
Jack让我不回去找他  是为了保护我
Jack told me not to come back to protect me,
他不想让我受到伤害
because he didn't want me to get hurt.
你这么想吗?
Is that what you think?
是的  我就这么想
Yeah, that's what I think.
我们在所有的笼子外都装有摄像机  Kate
We have cameras on the cages, Kate...all of them.
他看见你
He saw you.
你和Sawyer
you and Sawyer.
Jack让你不要回来的原因
The reason Jack told you not to come back
不是因为他怕你受到伤害
wasn't because he didn't want you to get hurt.
而是因为你伤了他的心
It was because you broke his heart.
所以...
So...
按住我的肩关节  然后把它扳回去
grab my wrist,push up and twist.
为什么要这么早来这里
Why do we gotta be out here so damn early?
因为你要我帮你抓只野猪
You asked me to help you catch a boar.
而现在正是它们出来觅食的时候
Well, this is when they break cover to eat.
好像它们都白天睡觉似的
Looks like they picked a day to sleep in.
你鱼钓得怎么样了  伙计
So what's your angle, brother?
钓鱼?
My angle?
你从来不怎么和我说话
Well, you...Haven't spoken three words to me,and then
怎么突然想做我的打猎伙伴?
suddenly you want to be my hunting partner.
钓鱼
My angle
正是我改变态度的原因
is I got hearts and minds to change,
这里行得通的就是贿赂
and politics is all about bribes.
既然钱在这里也没什么价值
Since money don't mean squat on this island,
我就得给人们一些他们想要的
I gotta give the people something they like.
大家都喜欢吃肉
And people like meat.
你肩膀怎么样了?
How's your shoulder?
非常好
Awesome.
那我们走吧
Then let's get going.
谢谢
Thank you.
不用谢  甜心
You're welcome, sweetheart.
天啊  对不起  真对不起
Oh, my god! I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- 没关系的  - 我真蠢
-No worries.  -I'm such an idiot.
这种事经常发生
It happens all the time, sweetheart.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你好  妈妈
Hi, mom.
你在这里干嘛  Katherine?
What are you doing here, Katherine?
你看起来不错
You look good.
我问你你来这里干什么
I asked you what you were doing here.
我想知道为什么你要告诉他们我对Wayne所做的事
I want to know why you told them what I did to Wayne.
我以为你来这里
I thought maybe you came because
是因为你想向我道歉
you wanted to say you were sorry.
我不感到抱歉
I'm not sorry.
他打你  把你当作狗来对待
He hit you. He treated you like a dog
而你...
and you...
你帮不了我的  Katherine
You can't help who you love, Katherine.
不管他是好是坏  我爱他
And for good or bad, I loved him.
而你却活活烧死了他
And you burnt him alive.
你打开了煤气  点了一把火
You turned on the gas, and you lit a match.
你无情地杀了他
You murdered him in cold blood.
我那么做都是为了你
I did it for you.
不
No.
你这么做是为了你自己
What you did, you did for yourself.
我要回去工作了
I have to go back to work.
因为你是我的女儿
Because you are my daughter,
我不会告诉坐在桌旁的
I'm not gonna tell the two men sitting at the table
那两个已经跟了我一个月的人
who've been following me for the last month
说你在这里
that you are here,
但我发誓  Katie
but I swear to god, Katie...
如果我再见到你
if I ever see you again,
我都会毫不犹豫地大声呼救
the first thing I will do is yell for help.
再见
Good-bye.
他跟你说了吗?
Did he say that to you?
说什么?
Sorry?
我伤了他的心
That I broke his heart.
他不说我也知道
He didn't have to.
你根本不了解他
You don't know anything about him.
我知道他在哪里出生
I know where he was born.
我知道他父母是做什么的
I know what his parents did for a living.
我知道他结婚了
I know that he was married
还知道他娶的是谁
and who he was married to.
我还知道他为什么离婚  他父亲是怎么死的
I know why he got a divorce. I know how his father died.
体重  生日  血型
his weight, his birthday and his blood type.
你对他又了解多少  Kate?
What do you know about him, Kate?
我们走吧
Let's go.
快跑
Run.
快跑!
Run!
快起来  起来!
Get up! Get up!
快跑  快点
Run! Run! Come on!
- 你在干什么?  - 我知道这个陷阱有多可怕
-What are you doing?  -I know what happens when you set those things off!
我们绕着走过去
We will go alongside them.
我们不需要  我们可以躲在另一边
We don't need to! We can go around there...off!
该死!
Damn it!
你还是过来这边比较好!
You're gonna want to be over here.
Kate  快过来
Kate, come on!
我们不知道那是什么
We don't know what it is,
但看起来它不怎么喜欢我们这个屏障
but we know that it doesn't like our fences.
你有钥匙
You had a key!
他们也把我丢下了  我也被毒气放倒了
They left me behind, too. They gassed me.
我知道你不怎么关心
I know that you don't care,
但那些过去三年来和我一起生活的人
but the people I spent the last three years of my life with
就这么把我扔下了
they just left me!
我想也许...
I thought that maybe...
也许我能让你觉得我们是一起的
Maybe if I could make you think that we were in it together.
也许我不会再一次被抛弃
Maybe I wouldn't get left behind again.
太美味了
It's delicious!
再来一点达摩A1  还有辣椒粉
Just a little Dharma A1 and paprika.
我希望你能在会议中记得提起这次烧烤
I hope you'll remember this little barbecue at your meeting later.
要开会吗?
Oh, what meeting?
Hurley告诉我关于投票的事
Hurley told me about the vote.
投票?  什么时候开始这里的人都要投票了
Vote? Since when did anyone around here vote?
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
根本就没什么投票
There wasn't ever gonna be no vote.
但是...这样不好么...和睦相处...
But...Wasn't it nice...Being nice?
你耍我让我变的像一个正直的人?
You tricked me into being decent?
- 这将是欺诈史上最槽糕的一次  - 这可不是欺诈  伙计
-That's gotta be the lamest con in the history of cons!  -It wasn't a con,dude.
如果你要成为我们暂时的领袖
If you're gonna be our temporary leader,
你必须要改变一切
you need to do some damage control.
领袖?  你到底在说些什么?
Leader? What the hell are you smoking?
Jack不在了  Locke不在了  Kate和Sayid...
Jack's gone. Locke's gone. Kate and Sayid...
就剩下你了
You're all we got.
Paulo和Nikki死时  我们都指望你
When Paulo and Nikki died,we all looked to you.
而你又想偷走他们的钻石
Then again, you totally tried to steal their diamonds,
但我们还是想指望你
but we wanted to look to you.
看看周围  你让所有人都很高兴
Look around.You made everyone happy.
只有今天  他们可以吃野猪肉
Just for today,they can eat boar,
开怀大笑  忘记他们的忧愁
laugh and forget that they're totally screwed.
这些都是你的功劳  伙计
And you did that for them, dude... You.
如果我不想当领袖呢?
And what if I don't want to be the leader?
我想Jack当初也不想当
Yeah, well, I don't think Jack wanted to, either.
你要试着习惯起来  老兄
Sucks for you, dude.
Sayid就在后院的一间屋子里
Sayid's in one of those backyards down there.
我会去找他
I'll go get him.
你应该去找Jack
You should get Jack.
Jack
Jack!
Jack  醒醒  是我
Jack, wake up. It's me.
出什么事了?
What happened?
他们都走了
They all left.
都走了?
What?
都是因为我
Because of me.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我应该听你的
I should've listened to you.
我不应该...
I never...
我只想回来救你...
I wanted to come back to help you...
但是你并不需要我
but you didn't need me to.
现在因为我  你不能回家了...
And now because of me, you can't go...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
真的很抱歉
他们就这么...
They just...
走了?
Left?
就连Juliet也走了?
Even Juliet?
不  他们把她也留下了
No, they left her, too.
为什么?
Why?
你比我更了解她
You know her better than I do.
现在怎么办?
Now what?
现在...
Now...
我们回去
Now we go back.
谢谢你为我所做的一切  Cassidy
Thanks for everything, Cassidy.
别客气
You got it.
那个抛弃你的家伙...
So... this guy who ripped you off...
你愿意告诉我他的名字吗?  告诉我哪儿能找到他?
You wanna give me his name, tell me where I can find him?
你差点因为我而被捕 Cassidy
You almost got arrested for me, Cassidy.
我想帮你
I wanna help you.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
是他的孩子
It's his.
孩子是他的  而且我还爱着他
The baby's his, and I still love him.
那么报警  把他关起来
So call the cops. Have him locked up.
你会原谅你母亲这么做吗?
Will you ever forgive your mom for calling the cops?
不
No.
不  我不会的
No, I won't.
谢谢你  Lucy
Thanks, Lucy.
我的名字是  Kate
My name's Kate.
你还好吗?
You okay?
是的  你呢?
Yeah. You?
还好
Yeah.
Jack
Sayid
我检查了所有的房间  所有人都走了
I've checked all the houses. Everyone's gone.
没留下任何武器和踪迹
No weapons, no trail.
就好像50多个人蒸发了一样
It's like 50 people disappeared into thin air.
我们拿上所有能找到的东西
We should take what we can find
趁天亮出发
and head out while we still got light.
她不能来
She is not coming with us.
不  她和我们一起回去
Yes, she is.
为什么?
Why?
因为他们把她也扔下了
Because they left her behind, too.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■